hungryhowies.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement | Hungry Howies

This policy describes how Hungry Howie's Pizza ("Hungry Howies") may use information collected from users of this site.  Hungry Howies reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and without sending notice to you, so you should review this Privacy Policy periodically.  The effective date of this notice and any revised or changed notice may be found on this page, on the upper left corner of the notice.

**Collection of Personal Information**

We may collect the following information from users who provide us this information in order to create an account and/or order from Hungry Howies or any of its independently owned and operated franchised restaurants or food service providers:  your name, your e-mail address, your phone number, your address, your credit card numbers, and your order history.  If you elect to establish an online account and/or order online, we have contracted with a third party to perform these functions for us, so that third party’s privacy policy and terms of use also apply.

Hungry Howies’ policy is to prohibit the unlawful disclosure of your personal information, but Hungry Howies makes no representation or warranties regarding the security or privacy of information that you may provide through this website.

Hungry Howies has entered into a joint marketing arrangement with our independently owned and operated franchised restaurants and/or food service providers and any information provided by you may be shared with our independently owned franchised restaurants and/or food service providers.  Hungry Howies may contact any individual who has shared personally identifiable information with Hungry Howies for sales and marketing purposes, for feedback about Hungry Howies and its services, or for any other reason logically related to the operation of Hungry Howie's business and agency.

**Online Technology**

Hungry Howies' website technology has the ability to collect data other than personally identifiable information. Hungry Howies may collect information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, or ISP domain name. Hungry Howies may collect information about the site you last visited prior to visiting a Hungry Howies website or about your activity during your visit to a Hungry Howies site. This information may be used by Hungry Howies to administer the technical and operational aspects of this site, and may include using your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Hungry Howies may use cookies (a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user) to assist in performing some or all of these activities. You can set your browser to accept all, some or no cookies. If you set your browser to reject all cookies, you may be limited in your ability to access some or all aspects of the site or be required to re-enter information.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

The preceding paragraphs describe the categories of personally identifiable information that Hungry Howies collects in this site.  Hungry Howies may disclose personally identifiable information you provide to third parties if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:  (a) complete the sales transaction, such as providing your payment or delivery information; (b) comply with legal process; (c) enforce the Terms of Use; (d) respond to claims that any information you provide violates the rights of third parties; (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Hungry Howies, its users and/or the public; or (f) in relation to the sale, assignment, transfer or acquisition of all or substantially all of Hungry Howie’s assets or shares by a third party.  Except as provided in the preceding sentence, Hungry Howies will NOT sell or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties, such as sellers of goods or services.

If you wish to change personally identifiable information that you have provided Hungry Howies, please _see the “Contact Hungry Howies” section below_.

**Tracking**

Hungry Howies will not recognize Web browser “do not track” signals.  If you would like additional information about online tracking and various opt-out mechanisms, please see <http://donottrack.us/>

Because Hungry Howies links to social media sites, and from time to time may include third-party advertisements, other parties may collect your personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you visit this site.

Please note that not all tracking will stop even if you delete cookies.

**Encryption**

Hungry Howies uses no encryption (data scrambling) on the site. When you are on any web site that asks you for confidential information, you should check to see if the information being transmitted is encrypted in order to increase the security of your information.  Keep in mind that there is no such thing as perfect security.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA")**

Hungry Howies complies fully with all aspects of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") in the collection and handling of personally identifiable information of children under the age of 13 and in the subsequent use of the data collected. No personally identifiable information will be collected from children under the age of 13 without parental consent in compliance with the COPPA guidelines. All personally identifiable information referred to in this statement is that collected from individuals 18 and over.

**Opt-Out**

If you want to "opt-out" of being contacted by Hungry Howies after you have shared your information, or you wish to correct the information you have provided, you may do so in one of two (2) ways:

Send email to [hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com](mailto:hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com); or,

Call (248) 414-3300 and ask to speak to Customer Service.

**Contact Hungry Howies**

If you wish to contact Hungry Howies to correct, amend, or delete information (if Hungry Howies is holding on to your information as explained above), about Privacy related issues or for any reason at all, you may do so by contacting Hungry Howie's Customer Service at:

            Mail to:           Privacy Policy c/o;

                                    Hungry Howie's Pizza, Inc.

                                    30300 Stephenson Hwy.

                                    Madison Heights, MI. 48071

Email to:          [hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com](mailto:hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com); or

Phone to: (248) 414-3300 and ask to speak to Customer Service.

**Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement**

Hungry Howies may link to other web sites created and maintained by other public and/or private organizations. Hungry Howies provides links to these sites as a service to our users. The presence of a link does not constitute Hungry Howies endorsement of the site.

When users follow a link to an outside web site, they are leaving Hungry Howies and are subject to the policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside web site(s). Hungry Howies is not responsible for the information collection practices of non- Hungry Howies sites.

**Additional Rights:**

Applicable laws may give you additional rights that are not described in this online privacy statement.

This statement describes how Hungry Howie's Pizza ("Hungry Howies") may use information collected from users of this site.

Collection of Personal Information

  * Hungry Howies makes no representation regarding the security or privacy of information that you may provide through this website. Hungry Howies may contact any individual who has shared personally identifiable information with Hungry Howies for sales and marketing purposes, for feedback about Hungry Howies and its services, or for any other reason logically related to the operation of Hungry Howie's business and agency.

Online Technology

  * Hungry Howies' website technology has the ability to collect data other than personally identifiable information. Hungry Howies may collect information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, or ISP domain name. Hungry Howies may collect information about the site you last visited prior to visiting a Hungry Howies website or about your activity during your visit to a Hungry Howies site. This information may be used by Hungry Howies to administer the technical and operational aspects of this site, and may include using your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Hungry Howies may use cookies (a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user) to assist in performing some or all of these activities. You can set your browser to accept all, some or no cookies. If you set your browser to reject all cookies, you may be limited in your ability to access some or all aspects of the site or be required to re-enter information.

COPPA

  * Hungry Howies complies fully with all aspects of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") in the collection and handling of personally identifiable information of children under the age of 13 and in the subsequent use of the data collected. No personally identifiable information will be collected from children under the age of 13 without parental consent in compliance with the COPPA guidelines. All personally identifiable information referred to in this statement is that collected from individuals 18 and over.

Opt-Out

  * If you want to "opt-out" of being contacted by Hungry Howies after you have shared your information, or you wish to correct the information you have provided, you may do so in one of two (2) ways: 
    1. Send email to [hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com](mailto:hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com).
    2. Call (248) 414-3300 and ask to speak to Customer Service.

Contact Hungry Howies

  * If you wish to contact Hungry Howies to correct, amend, or delete information (if Hungry Howies is holding on to your information as explained above), about Privacy related issues or for any reason at all, you may do so by contacting Hungry Howie's Customer Service at: 
    1. Mail to: Privacy Policy c/o;  
Hungry Howie's Pizza, Inc.  
30300 Stephenson Hwy.  
Madison Heights, MI. 48071
    2. Email to: [hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com](mailto:hhcustserv@hungryhowies.com); or
    3. Phone to: (248) 414-3300.

Linking Policy and Disclaimer of Endorsement

  * Hungry Howies may link to other web sites created and maintained by other public and/or private organizations. Hungry Howies provides links to these sites as a service to our users. The presence of a link does not constitute Hungry Howies endorsement of the site.
  * When users follow a link to an outside web site, they are leaving Hungry Howies and are subject to the policies of the owners/sponsors of the outside web site(s). Hungry Howies is not responsible for the information collection practices of non- Hungry Howies sites.
